(+91) 9119620847 Hyderabad, India prashant@cometlabs.in

# **Prashant Katiyar**

## Tech Entrepreneur | Product Manager

Portfolio: prashantkatiyar.com GitHub: prashantkatiyar9777 LinkedIn: prashant-milan-katiyar

Startup Founder with 3 years of experience building SaaS products in Developer Tools, Hiring, Web-3 and Retail Tech Startups, which generated over \$ 3.5 Million in revenue. I run a community of 1,20,000+ Developers, providing tools to show proof of work. I also raised \$ 150K (₹ 1.1 Cr) in Venture Capital for my startup in 2nd year of college, and got it acquihired.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Product Manager Mar 2024 – Present

Innovapptive Inc. Hyderabad, India

- Led the Product and Engineering Team in developing the next iteration of our B2B SaaS offering, Race 2.0.
- Directly reported to the CEO to craft a comprehensive year-long roadmap for the product leading up to its successful launch.
- Played a key role in hiring QA, Analysts, and Engineers to streamline processes within the product team.
- Utilized market research, customer feedback, and insights from sales to prioritize product requirements and user stories.
- Managed daily scrum calls authored detailed PRDs, and organized Jira boards, ensuring the efficient completion of sprints.

#### **Founder & Chief Product Officer**

May 2021 - Feb 2024

CometLabs (AcquiHired by Innovapptive Inc.)

Hyderabad, India

- Led the development of a cloud-based IDE utilizing Generative AI for code analysis and project evaluations.
- Secured INR 1.1 Cr preseed funding, served a thriving community of 120K developers & 18,000 active users.
- Built product from UI design to MVP; later supervised an 11-member engineering team.
- Established partnerships with GitHub and Vercel for seamless integrations to enhance the developer experience.
- · Adopted Agile workflows & Sprint Planning using tools like Confluence, Jira, Notion, Miro, Trello, etc.
- Outperformed competitors: 40% speedier load, 25% better efficiency, and 20% less browser memory usage within 8 months.

#### **Associate Product Manager**

Dec 2020 - Sep 2021

Hapramp Studios Gurgaon, India

- Headed Creator Studio division: launching 3 major updates & initiating 4 beta tests within a 5-month timeframe.
- Drafted PRDs for Binance Wallet & KYC integration, achieving 50K+ DAU and boosting GTV.
- Conducted A/B Testing to improve performance, amplifying ASPU by 37%, Token Sales by 42% while trimming TTV by 20%.
- Coordinated closely with a 13-member Tech & Design team to ensure timely project delivery.
- Explored new revenue models by introducing NFT Minting after analyzing Web3 Market, increased revenue by 12%.

Product Intern May 2020 – Dec 2020

Moptra Infotech

Noida/Remote, India

- Collaborated with Devs to refine a supply chain tool, enhancing user satisfaction by 15%.
- Integrated Amplitude, Google Analytics & CRM with e-commerce platforms, grew engagement by 12%.
- Led design sprints, optimized JIRA product roadmaps, and crafted PRDs based on user feedback.
- Conducted A/B tests on the e-commerce platform, driving a 10% boost in user conversions.

#### **SKILLS**

Product Management Tools Jira, Trello, Notion, Miro, Amplitude, Mixpanel, Metabase, Google Analytics

Product Design ToolsBalsamiq, Lucid Charts, Figma, Canva, RetoolProgramming LanguagesSQL, C, C++, Javascript, Python, BashFramework TechnologiesReactJS, NextJS, Tailwind, AWS, NodeJs.

Core Competencies Product Strategy, Business Analysis, User Research, Community Building, Persona Creation, Wireframing, Mockups, PRD, Product Roadmap, Agile Methodology, Sprint Planning, TDD,

UAT, A/B Testing, Product Analytics, Success Metrics, KPIs

### **EDUCATION**

**B. Tech. (ECE)**, *Indian Institute of Information Technology (IIIT)*, *Guwahati* **Entrepreneurial Studies (Seed Spark)**, *Stanford University Graduate School of Business* 

Apr 2023

July 2023

#### **ACTIVITIES**

Top 30 Finalist - HYSEA 10X Product Awards & Expo, Hyderabad
Top 5 Finalist - EO Global Student Entrepreneur Awards (GSEA), Goa & New Delhi
Founder - IIITians Network: Community of 59500+ Developers from IITs, IIITs

2023

2023

2021 - 2022